Contact

mebmck@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/megan-mckerr-74233195 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Nursing ACLS Epic Systems

Megan McKerr

Travel RN-PACU, BSN, CCRN, ACLS, PALS, TNCC at University of Kentucky Albert B Chandler Hospital

Farmville, North Carolina

Summary

Experienced Travel Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Post Anesthesia Care, Customer Service, Pediatric Advanced Life Support (PALS), Patient Education, and TNCC. Strong healthcare services professional with a BSN focused in Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse from University of North Carolina at Wilmington.

Experience

University of Kentucky Albert B Chandler Hospital Travel RN-PACU, BSN, CCRN, ACLS, PALS, TNCC July 2019 - Present (1 year)

Lexington, Kentucky

Vidant Medical Center
Staff Nurse II-SICU, BSN, CCRN, ACLS, PALS, TNCC
April 2019 - June 2019 (3 months)
Greenville, North Carolina

Hartford Hospital Travel RN-PACU, BSN, CCRN, ACLS, PALS, TNCC January 2019 - April 2019 (4 months) Hartford, Connecticut

Inpatient PACU

Palmetto Health-USC Medical Group Travel RN-PACU, BSN, CCRN, ACLS, PALS, TNCC June 2018 - September 2018 (4 months) Columbia, South Carolina

PACU

St. Mary's Health Care System
Travel RN-PACU, BSN, CCRN, ACLS, PALS, TNCC

September 2017 - April 2018 (8 months)

Athens, Georgia

PACU

Medical University of South Carolina Travel RN-PACU, BSN, CCRN, ACLS, PALS, TNCC June 2017 - September 2017 (4 months)

Charleston, South Carolina

PACU

Christiana Care Health System
Travel RN-PACU-BSN-CCRN-ALCS-PALS-TNCC-FCCS
February 2017 - May 2017 (4 months)

Newark, Delaware

PACU

Memorial Health
Travel RN-PACU-BSN-CCRN-ALCS-PALS-TNCC-FCCS
October 2016 - December 2016 (3 months)
Savannah, Georgia

PACU

The University of Iowa Health Care
Travel RN-PACU-BSN-CCRN-ALCS-PALS-TNCC-FCCS
May 2016 - September 2016 (5 months)
Iowa City, Iowa Area

PACU Travel RN

Johns Hopkins Hospital Travel RN-PACU-BSN-CCRN-ALCS-PALS-TNCC-FCCS January 2016 - April 2016 (4 months)

Baltimore, Maryland Area

PACU

Lifespan

Travel RN-PACU-BSN-CCRN-ACLS-PALS-TNCC-FCCS July 2015 - December 2015 (6 months)

Providence, Rhode Island

PACU

Wake Forest Baptist Health

Travel RN-PACU-BSN-CCRN-ALCS-PALS-TNCC-FCCS February 2015 - May 2015 (4 months)

Winston Salem, North Carolina

PACU

Massachusetts General Hospital Travel RN-PACU-BSN-CCRN-ALCS-PALS-TNCC-FCCS July 2014 - December 2014 (6 months)

Boston, Massachusetts

PACU

Vidant Medical Center
RN-SICU-TICU-NSICU-PACU-BSN-CCRN-ALCS-PALS-TNCC-FCCS
June 2005 - June 2014 (9 years 1 month)

Education

University of North Carolina at Wilmington BSN, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2002 - 2005)

Eckerd College

Bachelor of Science (BS), Marine Geology/Oceanography · (1993 - 1995)